{
    "id": "78cd04ab97d34cc2a6be0c03ece70b48",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The opposition called ........................... the resignation of the minister.",
            "description": "To call for is to demand.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c67503924f034ee4b2809de3a45f6b7e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Call ................................ the ambulance.",
            "description": "To call for something is to telephone for it.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ea16e164a854c4bb76bf745198cfb26"
        },
        {
            "question": "Emergency situations like these call ................................... swift action.",
            "description": "Call for can mean require. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7d4c2c0c9cfb43218e9430b4e2076aa2"
        },
        {
            "question": "We had to call ................................ a doctor because dad complained of uneasiness.",
            "description": "To call somebody in is to get them to pay a visit.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "999ba1cf86954f8886d4e0c9d34d7c6a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has a short fuse but he calms ................................... fairly quickly.",
            "description": "To calm down is to stop being angry.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "down",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9dc92b809465428ea0c032ba1dad574b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't care .............................. fish or meat. I eat veggies whenever possible.",
            "description": "To care for something is to like it.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "89572641edb740cda6cc8ca52391b456"
        },
        {
            "question": "She got carried ..................................... when she heard that she was the winner.",
            "description": "To get carried away is to get so emotional that you lose control.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "away",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "324e7561865e4efe9f9a65b4f38ad98c"
        },
        {
            "question": "They hoped that the new government would carry the infrastructure projects ....................................",
            "description": "To carry something forward is to make it progress. ",
            "answers": [
                "forward",
                "forth"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cf18f1faaa8448be8d21b27ccf636786"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our team carried ...................................... the first prize.",
            "description": "To carry off is to win.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c4a1be1407984a1a87dfb44bf303d2ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "The volunteers quietly carried .................................... with their work.",
            "description": "To carry on is to continue.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "off",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cad70103f4c340d8805984aceee13968"
        },
        {
            "question": "The party carried ................................ into the night.",
            "description": "Carry over can mean continue past a certain point.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0110b3b47e6342378113d28382a4dc89"
        },
        {
            "question": "In spite of the opposition, the government carried .................................. the reforms.",
            "description": "To carry through is to complete successfully.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "through",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7f5c2733092144d5b3c7261faf13b921"
        }
    ]
}